{
    "subject": "resource/Junior_Blue",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Junior Blue",
    "human_readable": "The name of Junior Blue is Junior Blue.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9846766591072083,
            "question": "What is the name of Junior Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9734189510345459,
            "question": "Is Junior Blue a person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9676116704940796,
            "question": "What is Junior Blue known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.898295521736145,
            "question": "Does Junior Blue have any other names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8876857161521912,
            "question": "What does Junior Blue do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8851311206817627,
            "question": "Is Junior Blue a real person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8762474060058594,
            "question": "Where is Junior Blue from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.730745255947113,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Junior Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6758604049682617,
            "question": "Is there anything else we should know about Junior Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6104997992515564,
            "question": "How can we learn more about Junior Blue?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Junior Blue is Junior Blue.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8280_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else we should know about Junior Blue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8280_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Junior Blue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8280_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Junior Blue from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8280_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8280_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about a character named \"Junior\" or \"Captain Blue Jr.\" across several contexts, supporting the statement that there is a person known as \"Junior Blue\". While the documents do not explicitly state this full name in every context, they consistently refer to characters using variations of \"Junior\" and \"Blue\", which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}